/* eslint-disable max-len */
type QuestQuestion = {
    question: string,
    options: string[],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: number,
}

export const QUEST_QUESTIONS: Record<string, QuestQuestion[]> =
{
  '3-A-i': [{
    question: 'Which type of machine learning algorithm involves a labeled dataset for training?',
    options: ['Supervised learning',
      'Unsupervised learning',
      'Reinforcement learning',
      'None of the above',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  }, {
    question: 'Which of the following learning algorithms involves discovering patterns or relationships in data without labeled examples?',
    options: ['Supervised learning',
      'Unsupervised learning',
      'Reinforcement learning',
      'None of the above',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 1,
  }, {
    question: 'Which of the following learning algorithms is similar to how a child learns to ride a bicycle, where they receive feedback based on their actions to improve their performance?',
    options: ['Supervised learning',
      'Unsupervised learning',
      'Reinforcement learning',
      'None of the above',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 2,
  }],
  '3-A-ii': [{
    question: 'In machine learning, how is a reasoner constructed for classification or prediction?',
    options: ['Adjusting the dataset',
      `Adjusting the reasoner's parameters from an initial state`,
      'Adjusting the training time',
      'Adjusting the algorithm used',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 1,
  }, {
    question: 'What is the process through which machine learning constructs a reasoner for classification or prediction by adjusting its internal representations?',
    options: ['Feature engineering',
      'Parameter tuning',
      'Dimensionality reduction',
      'Hyperparameter optimization',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 1,
  }, {
    question: 'Which step in the machine learning process involves adjusting the internal representations of a reasoner to improve its classification or prediction performance?',
    options: ['Training',
      'Evaluation',
      'Inference',
      'Regularization',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  }],
  '3-A-iii': [{
    question: 'Which type of learning algorithm would be most suitable for training a model on a labeled dataset to predict the sentiment of customer reviews?',
    options: ['Supervised learning',
      `Unsupervised learning`,
      'Reinforcement learning',
      'Semi-supervised learning',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  }, {
    question: 'Which technique would be most appropriate to train a model on a large dataset with numerous unlabeled samples to identify clusters or patterns?',
    options: ['K-means',
      'Decision tree classification',
      'Support vector machines',
      'Naive Bayes classification',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  }, {
    question: 'After training a model using a supervised learning algorithm on real-world data, what is the next step to evaluate the results?',
    options: ['Collect more data',
      'Fine-tune the models hyperparameters',
      `Measure the model's performance on a separate test dataset`,
      'None of the above',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 2,
  }],
  '3-A-iv': [{
    question: 'What is the purpose of using a cross-validation set in the machine learning process?',
    options: ['To determine the optimal hyperparameters for the learning algorithm',
      `To assess the performance of the model on unseen data`,
      'To label the training data for supervised learning',
      'To select the most relevant features for the model',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 1,
  }, {
    question: 'Which step in the machine learning process involves selecting a subset of the available data to evaluate the performance of the trained model?',
    options: ['Deciding what problem to solve',
      'Choosing a feature set',
      'Running the learning algorithm',
      'Using a test set to measure performance',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 3,
  }, {
    question: 'In the context of machine learning, what is the primary goal of feature selection during the preprocessing phase?',
    options: ['To reduce the dimensionality of the dataset',
      'To generate additional training data',
      `To optimize the hyperparameters of the model`,
      'To measure the performance of the model',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  }],
  '3-A-v': [{
    question: 'Which type of machine learning algorithm adjusts its internal representations by iteratively comparing its predictions to the actual outcomes and updating its parameters accordingly?',
    options: ['Supervised learning',
      `Unsupervised learning`,
      'Reinforcement learning',
      'Semi-supervised learning',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  }, {
    question: 'How does a neural network, a type of machine learning algorithm, adjust its internal representations during training?',
    options: ['By minimizing the difference between predicted and actual outcomes through backpropagation and gradient descent',
      'By discovering patterns and relationships in the data without requiring labeled examples',
      'By iteratively adjusting its clusters or centroids based on the input features',
      'By using a feedback loop of rewards and punishments to learn optimal behaviors',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  }, {
    question: 'How do neural networks learn and improve their performance by adjusting their internal representations?',
    options: ['By fine-tuning the dataset',
      'By adjusting the loss function',
      `By adapting the activation functions`,
      'By updating the weights and biases',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 3,
  }],
  '3-A-vi': [{
    question: 'Which type of machine learning algorithm is most suitable for training a model to classify emails as either spam or not spam?',
    options: ['Supervised learning',
      `Unsupervised learning`,
      'Reinforcement learning',
      'Semi-supervised learning',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  }, {
    question: 'Which type of machine learning algorithm is most suitable for grouping similar customer profiles based on their purchasing behavior?',
    options: ['Supervised learning',
      `Unsupervised learning`,
      'Reinforcement learning',
      'Semi-supervised learning',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 1,
  }, {
    question: 'Which type of machine learning algorithm is most suitable for training a model to play a game by learning through trial and error?',
    options: ['Supervised learning',
      `Unsupervised learning`,
      'Reinforcement learning',
      'Semi-supervised learning',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 2,
  }],
  '3-B-i': [{
    question: 'What is the primary purpose of the backpropagation learning algorithm in training a multilayer neural network?',
    options: ['To adjust the weights of the neurons based on the difference between predicted and actual outputs',
      `To optimize the activation functions used in the hidden units`,
      'To determine the optimal number of hidden layers in the network',
      `To calculate the output probabilities of the network's hidden units`,
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  }, {
    question: 'How are the weights of the neurons updated during the backpropagation learning algorithm?',
    options: ['By adjusting the weights based on the difference between predicted and actual outputs',
      `By comparing the weights to a predefined threshold value`,
      'By multiplying the weights with the error function gradient',
      'By randomly selecting new weights for the neurons',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  }, {
    question: 'What happens to the weights of the neurons in a multilayer neural network as a result of the backpropagation learning algorithm?',
    options: ['The weights remain unchanged',
      `The weights decrease towards zero`,
      'The weights increase towards one',
      'The weights are adjusted to minimize the prediction error',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 3,
  }],
  '3-B-ii': [{
    question: 'Why is feature encoding important in machine learning?',
    options: ['Feature encoding determines the number of hidden layers in a neural network.',
      `Feature encoding affects the efficiency of the feature selection process.`,
      'Feature encoding can impact the ability of machine learning algorithms to understand and process the data.',
      `The choice of features has no impact on the performance of machine learning algorithms.`,
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 2,
  }, {
    question: 'What is the role of humans in deciding which features to include in a dataset for machine learning?',
    options: ['Humans select the appropriate machine learning algorithm for the dataset.',
      `Humans determine the optimal number of hidden layers in a neural network.`,
      'Humans decide which characteristics or attributes to represent as features in the dataset.',
      'Humans adjust the hyperparameters of the machine learning model.',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 2,
  }, {
    question: 'Why is it important for humans to choose features carefully when creating a dataset for a machine learning model to predict housing prices?',
    options: ['To include factors such as square footage, number of bedrooms, and location that significantly influence housing prices.',
      `To determine the optimal number of hidden layers in a neural network.`,
      'To ensure the model trains quickly and efficiently.',
      'To adjust the learning rate of the machine learning algorithm.',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  }],
  '3-C-i': [{
    question: 'Which factor is important to consider when evaluating a dataset used to train an AI system in terms of storage requirements?',
    options: ['The size of the dataset',
      `The way the data were acquired and labeled`,
      'The estimated time to produce the dataset',
      `The variety of data types in the dataset`,
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  }, {
    question: 'Which aspect is most important to consider when evaluating a dataset used to train an AI system in terms of data acquisition and labeling?',
    options: ['The size of the dataset',
      `The storage requirements of the dataset`,
      'The diversity of the dataset',
      'The quality and accuracy of the labeling process',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 3,
  }, {
    question: 'In general, using more training data results in more accurate predictions on test data?',
    options: ['True',
      `False`,
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  }],
  '3-C-ii': [{
    question: 'Which type of demographic variables should be investigated to identify potential imbalances in training data that could result in a biased model?',
    options: ['Gender, age, and ethnicity',
      `Numerical variables and categorical variables`,
      'Feature importance and feature correlation',
      `Training time and model accuracy`,
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  }, {
    question: `How can data visualization help in identifying potential biases in a model's training data?`,
    options: ['By representing data in visually appealing ways',
      `By providing insights into feature importance and correlation`,
      'By highlighting imbalances in training data based on demographic variables',
      'By measuring the training time and model accuracy',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 2,
  }, {
    question: 'Which approach can be used to investigate imbalances in training data based on demographic variables?',
    options: ['Using a data visualization tool.',
      `Modifying the activation function of the neural network.`,
      'Applying feature scaling to the dataset.',
      'Assessing statistical measures such as mean and standard deviation.',
      'I don’t know'],
    indexOfCorrectAnswer: 0,
  }],
};
